For our studio's survival
We have to work hard.
Let's wrap up this meeting.
I'll send everyone the script a little later.
Thank you, everyone.
I want to ask each of you to make sure you take care of your own preparation work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hey, Cici.
Have a seat.
I have something I want to talk to you about.
What's wrong? There is nothing to worry about, don't overthink about it.
Okay, here. This is for you.
To be honest.
I didn't want this either.
It's just the way things are right now.
Let's shoot first.
But you might find that this may be very good money and lucrative.
And that's the only thing we'll be shooting after this project.
No, it won't.
Even adult films have storylines, do they not?
We can shoot it in to a high end quality movie.
All right, I got it.
Relax, you don't have to worry about a thing.
I'm not gonna jeopardize the quality of the movie just for the sake of making money.
Our studio will have less to worry about and be more stable after this project.
It won't be a problem to shoot other things after this project.
OK?
I see.
But…
But..... what's wrong?
Its just.....
I'm not really that experienced in that subject.