We have to work hard for our studio's survival.
Let's wrap up this meeting.
I'll send everyone the script a little later.
All right. I want to ask each of you to make sure you take care of your own preparation work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Cherry
Please stay here.
Have a seat.
I have something I want to talk to you about.
All right.
Can you give me a minute.
Wow, thank you.
Thank you.
How did you know that I like to drink iced Americano.
Please. You even drink Iced Americano during the Winter storms.
I see you drinking it every time.
It makes me feel so cold.
That's true.
Well, this time.
Will your husband not be able to stand it?
My husband…
Maybe before he couldn't.
We haven't spoken in days.
Huh?
I'm sorry to hear that..
I didn't want to say anything.
It's okay. Work is just work.
Anyways.
I've done travel shoots for people before.
But this is the first time I'm doing a porno.
Really?
For shooting these sex scenes
We need to find some reference pictures as examples.
Otherwise, we will just be communicating on the fly as we shoot.
And it will be difficult to explain what we want by words.