There’s something I want to announce to everyone.
We have a very special project.
It's not like anything we have filmed or shot before
So, that's why I wanted to talk to all of you about it.
Our new client produces adult films
So
We will be taking on their adult film project & production soon.
Wow, great!
Are we sure we don't want to look at other clients & producers?
Do you really think it's a good idea to make such a big transition like this?
Wow, Awesome!
If that's the case.
I can buy a lot of sexy and gorgeous clothes.
Especially lingerie.
Shooting this shouldn't be a problem.
I got nothing agaisnt it.
It will just take some time to work out all the kinks.
Can you tell everyone for me.
We will have a meeting later.
There is a new case that I want to talk about with everyone
Sure. No problem.
Can we do 1pm?
Alright see you at 1.
okay
OK.
All right.
We’ll have a meeting at 1pm.