Hey! Don't run!
Pay back the money you owe!
Bring me my production costs...
Senior classmate
What are you doing?
Did you stay up all night yesterday?
Were you gaming all night again.?
No.
Come on get up, wake up!
We need to get to work soon
Hurry up.
You slept on the couch again.
You still need to take care of yourself while you're working on a case.
You got me?
I’ll buy you a cup of coffee later.
Oh, yeah.
You want your usual an iced Americano, right?
OK
Wait a second.
Can you tell everyone for me.
We will have a meeting later.
There is a new case that I want to talk about with everyone
Sure. No problem.
Can we do 1pm?
Alright see you at 1.
OK.
All right.
OK
We’ll have a meeting at 1pm.
OK.