How was the shoot today?
Did it go the way you thought it would
or was it different?
It was okay.
I think next time there will be still
more room for improvement
And
You were just
really amazing
You were really hard
Oh, my!.....
How awkward
Stop teasing me
I had no choice
I didn't want to do it either.
Okay
Uh, are you busy later?
Let's go somewhere else to chat.
Sure, ok
but
I'll be right back
There are a few angles that I really wasn't happy with
What can we do?
But I just re-watched the playback
it looked okay
You did really good
Whatever…..
I'm just not happy with it.
Do you know how long it's been since I've been fucked?
Constantly seeing people fucking in front of me
how can I concentrate?