Are you okay
today?
Of course I am
Look how beautiful I made Bebe look with her makeup
It's really good not bad at all
today?
Are you tired
from earlier?
Omg…Argh
stop talking about it
Ugh….!
Are you free after work?
Why don't you join me for a drink
After all we've been working hard for so many days
You look like you were enjoying yourself at work today
Did you forget that you were at work?
I had no choice
It's just acting
Acting.....Acting
I know how to do it too.
That's what I ask of from my actors too
Is that a good
way to perform?
Oh
Oh, really?
Well then, I'm sorry to have to put you through this
The wine here is very good.
but
I think
that this will get me drunk
And yours?