Sure.
It's been a while since I visited your place.
Wait.
Your dad's home, right?
I don't have money to pay him back right now.
Don't worry.
He's out of the country.
That's why I'm here to watch over the place today.
Johnny.
You can leave now.
Well...
I’ll get out too.
How do I open this door?
Hey...
Bobby.
Do you like me?
What?
I said...
Do...
you...
like...
me?
What?
What are you talking about?
I don’t dislike you.
But...
like?
What kind of "like"?
What do you mean by "like"?
Actually, I've admired you for a long time.
This time...
It was me...
who pleaded with my dad for a long time to get you this filming opportunity.
Actually, back on set...
Actually...
What actually?
I didn’t expect to feel...
a little bitter.
I should be...
prettier than Bebe, right?
You are quite pretty.
Wow...
You...
Bobby...
I won’t force you.
This...
Do you like it this way?
L-l-like it.