What's going on?
You're a pain in the ass!
Cici
Just give me a minute
give me a minute
you
Are you ok
I have no idea
I can't describe the feeling
I'm just in a weird mood right now
Me too
My mood is
really complicated
But after I was done shooting
The first thing I thought of
was you
Did you miss me?
I hope you are not only thinking about perverted things
I
I'm kind of new to being on camera, it was like loosing my virginity
and In a nutshell
you should give me a red envelope ( Chinese custom )
so where is it at?
What the hell are you talking about?
I was just concerned about you
do you want to take a walk with me?
Oh, okay
Do you remember
The first time you
were in a movie and how it felt?
You mean just now?
No not that.
I meant
The reason why you made your first movie.
I can't remember what you were like before
all I can see in my mind
is you
completely naked