What about your husband?
I remember
you've been married for about three or four years?
It's just that our work and lifestyle routine doesn't match up!
We
have been sleeping in different rooms for awhile now.
I see
but
In that case
if you feel lonely
you can call me!
What are you saying
you're so gross
Don't just think you can talk like that, just because you were in a porno
No not that.
I was just teasing and joking
Don't be so serious.
Forget about it!
You wouldn't understand anyways
Are you ok
Do you want me to give you a ride home?
It's all right.
I'll just take the bus home myself.
I guess we'll be busy with editing tomorrow.
Go home and get some rest.
You sure you're ok
are you sure?
Yes