Director, it's time to wrap it up for the day!
Stop calling me that...
Actually,
how do you think
we're doing so far?
I think it's really good so far!
Your acting is amazing!
You should really consider getting into acting full time!
I was talking about the whole movie!
Overall it's really good.
It might possibly be a hit movie.
I can't wait for the finished movie!
Oh!
But...
being naked in front of  so many people that I know
and fucking in front of them
I really don't know how to face them in the future!
AH!
Stop worrying about it so much.
I can see that the team is really good at what they do!
Besides, it's not like I haven't seen you butt naked before!
When we were kids we took baths together.
We were little kids at that time, that was different.
But
it's true we have matured a lot now.
Oh yeah!
Do you want to come over later?!