Alright
don't think about it too much.
Next
those videos just
give them to the editing team.
Wow!
you
want to have another drink?
Sure thank you.
Boss man another round!
Wow!
Here you go…here you go…..
Thank you so much!
Cheers
ok
Did you know
Me and my husband
because of our work
our lifestyle routines are different.
We've been sleeping in different rooms for awhile now,
But we're in the movie business
and it's hard work
If I get to have a meal with him just once a week
It is a luxury to me.
He said how can we even have a baby!
but
It's getting pretty late.
so…
Let's call it a day
and hurry up and go home.
One Day
won't change anything.
and
At this hour
he's already in bed and asleep.
and I've been drinking.
I don't want to go home!
but
Don't tell me
you're going back to the office to sleep.
Then can you help find me a hotel?
As long as there's a bed I'll be good.
I'm a little drunk!
Be careful.
Are you ok
Let's go to the bed.
To the bed
Ok…ok...
Let's go…go..go
Watch your step
be carful.
hold on tight.
Ok…Ok…..Ok
Sit here first…..
Take a seat
Ok…Ok…..Ok
Have a seat for a little bit
I'll go get you some water!
Go…...
No….No….
No…
Keep me company for just a little longer
don't leave yet.
Kiss me….
What! You're drunk!
Stop talking!
My ears
I want it
I want!
Wait….Wait
What's wrong?
Your cell phone is ringing.
It's ok….
Who cares..... Don't worry about it.
Just ignore it!
Are you sure......?
It's ok….
Your cell phone keeps ringing.
Wait….Wait
Hello
Yes
We just called it a day.
I'll be home a little later.
Okay, go to bed
ok
good night
Goodbye
Your husband?
Nothing, it's fine.
Everything is fine.
I said we
....Never mind it's nothing.
I know what you mean
but
You'd better go home.
See you at the warap up party.