It taste pretty good
Let me ask you a question
when you were just on the set
I caught a glimpse of your expression that was on your face
you
were you secretly excited?
I didn't think you
would be so amazing
Have you
you been practicing on the side?
I didn't practice at all
I'm drunk, I need to go to a restroom
If you need makeup you should ask me (In Chinese restroom sounds like makeup room)
No I need to use the restroom
the restroom
Director
Did you know
I have always liked you?
Can't you tell?
Isn't It really obvious
You're really drunk
No I'm not
I couldn't believe you just cummed all over Bebe's body.
and you still have a hard-on.
You're amazing.
No I'm not
you can
Director, you're so hard
Director why are you so hard stll
Anyone there?
hey!
Yes I'm here