Alright, come on.
For today
Let's stop here, that's pretty much it.
Let's get off work early.
I'm so tired.
Everyone did a great job
for the last few days.
I think
we should
still have a wrap up party.
Are we going to have some drinks?
Sure…ok…yes…ok
But Bobby
You still owe a lot of money!
It's better if we don't celebrate.
It's okay, don't worry.
I'm still hanging on for the time being.
Any ways
It's been a long time since we'd kicked back and had a relaxing drink together.
Right?
What do you think?
Do you want to go to the Izakaya bar or the karaoke bar?
Your choice.
Since we are going out
why don't we go to my friend's club?
His place is quite special
and most importantly
If I go there I get a discount.
Let me show you some pictures.
Wow!
This place looks awesome,
but it looks a little bit like…..
Cherry
you're too shy
Didn't you say you didn't have much experience with sex.
His club's performers and performances
are amazing!
Maybe
You can take advantage of
learning some new things!
Ahh…Ok…Ok …Ok
Then let's go there!
I need to go home and change into something sexier.
Bobby can you give me a ride home?
Bobby should be taking me instead!
After all, it's my friend's club.
And most importantly
I still need to
teach him a few things, so he can learn them properly!
Or Bobby
maybe you can check my receipts & expenditures first?
I'd like to get them done before the wrap up party!