As a matter of fact
Why didn't you
take a shower at home?
Why did you come here to shower?
Sigh!
You think
if I took a shower at home
and wore a sexy out fit.
What do you think my husband will think!
He would follow me all the way to the club.
How could we celebrate like that!
So that's why.
But
it feels like I'm deceiving him.
Is that okay?
Just think of it as a white lie.
and most importantly
Even if I explained it clearly to him
he would still act the same way.
He still wouldn't want to get divorced.
It would be better not to
tell him anything.
it's like that!
But
it still feels like we are betraying him.
Doesn't it feel exciting
feeling up another guy's wife?
Doesn't it feel like a role from a porno?
OMG
Indeed
It feels like
I am cuckolding him!
Sure enough
isn't it interesting?
If you're done touhing
can you get me a towel?
What if I want you later and I can't wait.
Alright!