Cici
You're very thorough, aren't you?
Oh no…
it's really late!
It's too late!
Sleepy head
time to get out of bed!
What time is it?
I forgot to wake you up!
We still have a couple of hours.
I've slept for that long?
I still haven't changed my clothes yet.
What should I do?
I'm sorry
I thought that
I should let you get some sleep.
Now what?
I can't go dressed like this.
Maybe
you can go to Rosie's closet to see
if there is anything
you can wear!
I think she has a lot of great looking out fits.
Okay, I'll go and take a look.
Ok, go, go, go, go.
take a look!
Her pajamas are so strange.
Look at
this one!
How do you wear such sexy pajamas?
Maybe
you should wear
this one!
Think of it as cosplay!
That is too embarrassing to wear!
Actually
you really don't have any other choices.
I guess
It is what it is.
Go get changed.
Don't you dare peek!