Everyone's been working hard lately.
Come here.
Let's have a toast.
Sure!
Cheers everyone!
Cherry, drink some more!
What are you drinking?
You only had a little bit to drink!
I had too much!
Are you nursing your drink?
No
Since you sobered up
why don't you drink more!
He sobered up
Are you nursing your drink?
You there
drink more!
Cheers! Drink up!
What are you doing?
Why aren’t you drinking with us?
Hurry up and drink!
I want to see you drink.
Hurry up ! I want to watch you drink!
It burns!
Does it burn?!
You see, you don't go out drinking much.
It's doesn't burn.
I'm telling you, you really need to drink this.
You have to drink more.
Cheers
Take it in one shot!
Aww look at you, all grown up now!
Our kids are all grown up now!
So good!
Why are you stopping? Keep drinking!
Come on, let's keep drinking!
Hurry up!
I'm tired.
It's all right.
Drink up.
What's Bobby doing?
Bobby is nursing his drink!
Drink up.
Is he not in the mood to drink?
He wants to drink that drink.
Drink up.
You're so weak!
Are you trying to avoid drinking?
Bobby I will drink with you!
Cheers
Cherry, why aren't you drinking?
Drink up Ms. Cherry!
Cheers! Cheers!
Bottoms up!
Drink up.
I want more!
The 2 of you are having fun now!
So happy!
So adorable… How adorable!
What are you wearing today?
All dressed up!
Oh, yeah, it's a little embarrassing.
Mmm.. Yes you are really embarrassing
I have so many different sexy outfits in my closet
and you pick the most conservative outfit I have!
Are you in pre-school dressing like that!
Wearing that…..
Wearing that who would flirt with you!
No man will ever approach you dressed like that.
Listen up, everybody!
Let me tell you something
I've prepared a little something for Bobby!
It's a speacial performance!
What!
Let me go get them.
You better wait for me!