Why are you leaning so closely?
Are you shy!?
Haven't you been to a club before?
It wasn't the same as this.
Take a look at Sis and Cherry they are watching.
But I only like you!
Are you drunk or something?
No, it's truly from my heart.
Let's go!
Bobby, come in here!
This is your room!
That's right.
It looks so warm and cozy.
I guess I'll sit over here.
Sure!
Have a seat.
You really do look cute.
But are you sure you want to do this?
I'm sure.
I really like you Bobby!
Oh, is that so?
Do you like me that much?
I want a kiss from you first.
Okay
One more!
Very good!
Give me more tongue!
Ok
Let me taste your tongue!
Is it sweet!
It's really sweet.
It's so cute.
Are you sure you really want to do this?
I'm sure. I'm not drunk.
I'm not drunk.
Please take off your coat first.
It's unbuttoned now.
it is hard to imagine
how much
you take care of your skin!
Its so soft!
I'm going to help you take off your underwear now.
Do you really want me?
Yes I want you!
Then I'm going to strip you naked now.
What's the matter? Are you shy?
Just a little bit sensitive.
Come here, stand up.
Take off your skirt!
Ok!
Its so soft!