I think it's time
Let me help you catch up with a class!
Hah!!! catch up with a class?!!!
It doesn't matter if it is music class
or PE class
I don't think you're even familiar with either!
Are you going to teach me?
I really like to learn!
Come with me.
Come!
What do you think?
Here
I have prepared something just for you!
say something!
I wish I had met you earlier.
I keep looking at you
wondering why you are so good looking?
My ears are itching!
Your ears are that sensative?
Yes!
You're that sensitive!
Will cum faster then me?
You're so bad!
I'm here to teach you
Step by step!
You're tongue is so soft!
Bobby
Wow!
Your titts are so big!
Lower!
They are so big and soft!
You're such a horny slut!
I think
it's been a long time since I had sex!
It looks like you really know how to suck on a dick!
Take your clothes off I want to see more!
What about here!
You'r boobs are so pretty.
Your hands are so warm!
Wow!
I can see
how hard your nipples are!
Do you like it?
They're so pretty.
Let's go inside
Bobby
help me….
help me take off my clothes!
What do you think?
Bobby
is your
cock hard yet?
Yes.
Sweety
I want to see more!
I want to see your pussy!
I can't handle it anymore!
Bobby
your dick is not being a good boy!
It's all your fault!
Then
next
what do you want to do?